<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="wrap_content"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
    android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">

    <LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
        xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
        android:id="@+id/activity_dvalore"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
        android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
        android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
        android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        tools:context="bigmarbz.overwatch.dvalore"
        android:weightSum="1">


        <TextView
            android:text="Hana Song"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="40dp"
            android:textAppearance="@style/Base.ThemeOverlay.AppCompat"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:id="@+id/textView8"
            android:layout_gravity="center_horizontal"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true" />


        =

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="196dp"
            app:srcCompat="@drawable/dvalore"
            android:id="@+id/imageView2" />

        <TextView
            android:text="Background"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="20dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
            android:textAppearance="@style/Base.ThemeOverlay.AppCompat"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:id="@+id/textView11"
            android:layout_gravity="center_horizontal"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"  />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Hana Song was once a pro-gamer. She became a professional StarCraft player, who participated in the WCS Korea Code S League. At the age of 16, Song became the #1 ranked player in the world and proceeded to go undefeated for the next three years in all competitions. She became an international star, beloved by her fans at home and abroad, and toured in exhibitions around the world. A fierce competitor, Song played to win at any cost, and gained a well-earned reputation for showing no mercy to her opponents. At home, however, not all was well, as MEKA struggled to maintain its defense against the omnic that repeatedly attacked the nation. As the omnic continued to adapt, it eventually disrupted MEKA's drone-control networks, forcing the military to place pilots in the mechs. Scrambling to find suitable candidates, the government turned to the country's professional gamers, who possessed the necessary reflexes and instincts to operate the mechs' advanced weapons systems. Top stars were drafted, including Song. Seeing her new mission as a game, Song now fearlessly charges into battle alongside the rest of her MEKA unit, ready to spring to her nation's defense at a moment's notice. Recently, she has begun to stream combat operations to her adoring fans, and her growing following has turned her into a global icon. At some point she also played one of the leading roles in the movie Hero of My Storm."></TextView>


    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>